#------------------------------TRY IT YOURSELF : 1.0----------------------------------------------#

Note : Solution well be in SOLUTION Folder.

Restaurant: Make a class called Restaurant. The __init__() method for
Restaurant should store two attributes: a restaurant_name and a cuisine_type.
Make a method called describe_restaurant() that prints these two pieces of
information, and a method called open_restaurant() that prints a message
indicating that the restaurant is open.

Make an instance called restaurant from your class. Print the two attributes
individually, and then call both methods.

Three Restaurants: Start with your class from Exercise 9-1. Create
three different instances from the class, and call describe_restaurant() for
each instance.

Users: Make a class called User. Create two attributes called first_name
and last_name, and then create several other attributes that are typically
stored in a user profile. Make a method called describe_user() that prints a
summary of the user’s information. Make another method called greet_user()
that prints a personalized greeting to the user.

Create several instances representing different users, and call both
methods for each user.

#--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------#

#------------------------------TRY IT YOURSELF : 1.1----------------------------------------------#

Number Served:  Add an attribute called number_served with a default value of 0.
Create an instance called restaurant from this class. Print the number of customers
the restaurant has served, and then change this value and print it again.
Add a method called set_number_served() that lets you set the number of
customers that have been served. Call this method with a new number and
print the value again.

Add a method called increment_number_served() that lets you increment the
number of customers who’ve been served. Call this method with any
number you like that could represent how many customers were served in,
say, a day of business.

Login Attempts: Add an attribute called login_attempts to your User
class from Exercise 9-3 (page 162). Write a method called
increment_login_attempts() that increments the value of login_attempts by 1.
Write another method called reset_login_attempts() that resets the value of
login_attempts to 0.

Make an instance of the User class and call increment_login_attempts()
several times. Print the value of login_attempts to make sure it was
incremented properly, and then call reset_login_attempts(). Print
login_attempts again to make sure it was reset to 0.

#--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------#
