#------------------------------TRY IT YOURSELF : 1.0----------------------------------------------#

Note : Solution well be in SOLUTION Folder.

Restaurant: Make a class called Restaurant. The __init__() method for
Restaurant should store two attributes: a restaurant_name and a cuisine_type.
Make a method called describe_restaurant() that prints these two pieces of
information, and a method called open_restaurant() that prints a message
indicating that the restaurant is open.

Make an instance called restaurant from your class. Print the two attributes
individually, and then call both methods.

Three Restaurants: Start with your class from Exercise 9-1. Create
three different instances from the class, and call describe_restaurant() for
each instance.

Users: Make a class called User. Create two attributes called first_name
and last_name, and then create several other attributes that are typically
stored in a user profile. Make a method called describe_user() that prints a
summary of the user’s information. Make another method called greet_user()
that prints a personalized greeting to the user.

Create several instances representing different users, and call both
methods for each user.

#--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------#

